Finding Aid for the Collection of Tract Maps and Cadastral Maps of Southern California LSC.0349
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Venice of America (shows canals)., LA 49 C, 4-5. (Folder 5)
- Venice of America Replat no. 3., LA 49 C, 3-4.
- Venice of America-Ocean Park Villa Tract no. 2., LA 49 B, 4. (Box 1)
- Venice Park Tract., LA 49 C, 4.
- Venice Park Tract., LA 49 C, 3.
- Venice Vista Tract., LA 49 C, 4.
- Venice, Canals., LA 49 C, 4-5.
- Venus Canal and Part of Club House Place., LA 49 B-C, 4.
- Vermont Avenue Villa Tract., LA 51 E-F, 3. (Box 3)
- Vermont Avenue Villa Tract., LA 51 F, 3. (Box 3)
- Vicente Terrace Tract (Seaside Terrace on back)., LA 49 A, 2. (Box 3)
- Walgrove., LA 49 D-E, 3.
- Walgrove., LA 49 D-E, 3.
- Walker Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Walnut and Bean Land Company, (?)., 1880s; LA 56 A-F, 1-5.
- Ward Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Washington Gardner Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Washington Park, (?)., 1912; LA 50 C, 1. (Folder 5)
- Washington Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Wave Crest Tract., LA 49 A-B, 1-2.
- Wellsley Tract., LA 41 C-D, 3-4.
- West Adams and Washington Boulevard Tract, 1912.; LA 43 A, 4. (Box 1)
- West Lake Park Tract., LA 44 B, 2.
- Western Avenue Square, 1913.; LA 51 D-E, 2-4.
- Western Heights., LA 43 D, 4.
- Westgate., LA 41 C, 3.
- Westgate Heights., LA 41 A-B, 1-3. (Box 1)
- Westmoreland Place and Tract, 1902.; LA 44 A, 2-3.
  See: LA 43 F, 2-3.
- Westmoreland Place and Tract, 1902.; LA 43 F, 2-3. (Box 1)
- Westwood Hills., LA 41 E-F, 1. (Box 3)
  See: LA 32 E-F, 5-6.
- Westwood Hills., LA 32 E-F, 5-6.
- Wheeler Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Widow Botiller Tract., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Wiliamson Tract, 1886.; LA 44 C, 4. (Folder 7)
- Williamson Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Willmore, Official Plat of the Town of, (?)., 1880s; LA 75 C-D, 4-5. (Folder 4)
- Wilmington., LA 74 A-E, 2-5.
- Wilmington Harbor Park Tract., LA 74 B-C, 5.
- Wilshire Assessment District, Proposed., LA 44 A-D, 1-3.
  See: LA 33 D-F, 5-6.
- Wilshire Assessment District, Proposed., LA 43 A-F, 1-3.
- Wilshire Assessment District, Proposed., LA 42 D-F, 1-3.
- Wilshire Assessment District, Proposed., LA 35 D-F, 5-6.
- Wilshire Assessment District, Proposed., LA 34 A-F, 5-6.
- Wilshire Assessment District, Proposed., LA 33 D-F, 5-6. (Folder 2)
- Wilshire Boulevard Heights., LA 43 F, 2. (Box 1, 3)
- Wilshire Heights., LA 43 C, 1-2. (Box 3)
- Wodlen Mill Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Wolfskill Tract, 1893.; LA 44 D, 4. (Folder 7)
- Wood North Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Wright Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Wright's Addition., LA 49 E, 4.
- Wright's Addition to Ocean Park., LA 49 E, 4.